Location: Philadelphia, PA
Email: johnny.woo.park@gmail.com

Phone: 267-709-8266

# Johnny Park

<u>linkedin.com/in/johnny-park-073603114/</u> jpark42.github.io/portfolio-website/index.html

Software Engineering apprentice at Careerfoundry looking to become a Full-Stack Developer in the Philadelphia/DC area. Javascript-focused developer honing skills in C#. Seeking a workplace that is collaborative and fast-paced, while promoting a healthy environment of work-life balance. Ideal employer would value innovation and employee contribution towards projects. As an employee, I value opportunities for advancement & job security. I am an Insurance Broker with 4 years of experience working with clients in the Middle-Market sector and have decided to pivot my career towards software engineering to create applications that make more of a tangible impact to the clients I serve. With my experience with insurance and consulting, I can bring a risk management approach to programming to help protect consumer and company data, while having the soft-skills to effectively communicate with clients.

# Technologies and Languages

• Languages: HTML, CSS, Javascript, C#

Technologies: MongoDB, Express, Node.js, React.js, Bootstrap
 Soft skills: Goal setting, public speaking, customer service

Interests: Basketball, weight-lifting, kdramas, anime, self-help books, and electronic music duo Honne

# **Projects**

#### **AnimeFlix**

- Developed a scalable, single page application for 10+ users to login, sign-up, and view info about their favorite Anime movies.
- Created with MERN stack and implemented CRUD functionality, JSON web-token authentication, and password hashing.
- Utilizes a RESTful API to store and display movie and user info.

#### **Pokedex App**

Application built using HTML, CSS, Javascript, and Bootstrap that loads data from an external Pokemon API, featuring a functional search bar.

#### Education

CareerFoundry, Online
 2022—Present

Full-Stack Web Development Program

Anticipated Graduation Date: June 2023

• Temple University, Fox School of Business, Philadelphia, PA

2015-2019

Bachelor of Business Administration, in Risk Management & Insurance, GPA: 3.46

# **Work Experience**

Associate Broker Aon Risk Services 2021—Present Middle Market Philadelphia, PA

- Lead/aided brokering a \$6M book of business in property & casualty lines consisting of clients in Life Science, Technology, Healthcare, Public Entity, Food/Manufacturing, and Governmental Contracting industries in the Middle Market sector.
- Assist placements of accounts by curating loss summaries, schedules of insurance, renewal proposal presentations, benchmark analysis
  reports, coverage and rate comparisons, and policy checks.
- Responsible for all aspects of client service for assigned book of business including billing, policy collection, reviewal and transmittal
  documents in accordance with established departmental service standards.

Account Executive Valley Forge Insurance Brokerage 2019–2021

Account Management

Bala Cynwyd, PA

Responsible for servicing and renewing over 1,000 existing lawyer's professional, inland marine, ocean marine, small business owners, and
workers compensation accounts on an annual basis, while maintaining an 85% retention rate.

- Review all renewal submissions for completeness and acceptability, ensure proper contract file set-up, and distribute quotes and bind orders.
- Process requests for endorsements, certificates of insurance, loss runs, and answer coverage questions.

# **Leadership/Activities**

| • | Insurance Society of Philadelphia (NextGen), Events Coordinator                                | 2022–Present |
|---|--|--------------|
| • | Property & Casualty Career Development Committee, Member                                       | 2018-2019    |
| • | Gamma Iota Sigma Professional Risk Management, Insurance and Actual Science Fraternity, Member | 2017-2019    |

Temple University Big Brothers Big Sisters, Social Media Coordinator

2017-2019

2017-2019